Thank you so much for joining us.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Canvas family.
Welcome to our 9 a.m. service.
My name is Michelle Meeks and I'm the children's pastor here at Canvas.
I wanted to give you some announcements.
Before our service and I also wanted to let you know how our service is going to run today.
As it's a little bit different than the day.
I wanted to give you some announcements before our service.
And I also wanted to let you know how our service is going to run today.
As it's a little bit different than services in the past.
So for announcements.
We have a Canvas connection coming up January 23rd.
We're going to let you know how our service is going to run today.
As it's a little bit different than services in the past.
So for announcements.
We have a Canvas connection coming up January 23rd.
After the second service.
We plan to have this at the Mexican restaurant.
Right next to the Alamo.
Around 12:30.
If that's something that you want to know.
If you want to know how our service is going to run today.
As it's a little bit different than services in the past.
So for announcements.
We have a Canvas connection coming up January 23rd.
After the second service.
We plan to have this at the Mexican restaurant.
Right next to the Alamo.
Around 12:30.
If that's something that you are interested in joining us at.
Please sign up on our website.
To let us know that you plan to attend.
As for our service today.
Donovan is here to lead us in worship.
As many of you have heard.
Ryan is recovering from COVID.
So we have a special speaker here.
With our service.
One of our leadership members.
Andy Culp.
Is here with today's message.
And then after today's message.
Pastor Brandon.
Is here to give us an update.
On himself.
And his family.
Which we would love for you to stick around.
And hear.
That is all I have for you.
This morning.
So let's sing.
Who am I that the highest king.
Would welcome me.
I was lost but he brought me in.
Oh his love for me.
Oh.
would welcome me. I was lost, but He brought me in. Oh, His love for me. Oh, His love for me.
Oh, the sun sets free. Oh, His free indeed. I'm a child of God. Yes, I am.
Read lest He has ransomed me. His grace surrounds me. While I was a slave to sin, Jesus died
for me. Yes, He died for me. Oh, the sun sets free. Oh, is free indeed. I'm a child of God.
Yes, I am. In my Father's house, there's a place for me. I'm a child of God.
Yes, I am. I am chosen, not forsaken. I am who you say I am. You are for me, not against me.
I am chosen, not forsaken. I am who you say I am. And you are for me, not against me.
I am who you say I am. I am who you say I am. Oh, I am who you say I am.
Oh, the sun sets free. Oh, the sun sets free. Oh, is free indeed. I'm a child of God.
Yes, I am. In my Father's house, there's a place for me.
In my Father's house, there's a place for me. I'm a child of God. Yes, I am.
You are here, moving in our midst. I worship you. I worship you. You are here, working in this place. I worship you. I worship you.
Sing it out. You are.
You are my way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper, light in the darkness. My God, that is who you are.
You are here, touching every heart. I worship you. I worship you. I worship you.
I worship you. I worship you. You are here, healing every heart. I worship you. I worship you.
You are here, healing every heart. I worship you. I worship you. You are here, turning lives around. I worship you. I worship you.
I'm turning lives around. I worship you. I worship you. You are here, mending every heart. I worship you. I worship you, Lord.
Cause you are my way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper, light in the darkness. My God, that is who you are.
You are my way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper, light in the darkness. My God, that is who you are.
Yes, that is who you are.
That is who you are.
Even when.
Sing it out.
Even when I don't see it, you're working.
Even when I don't feel it, you're working.
You never stop.
You never stop working.
Even when I don't see it, you're working.
Even when I don't feel it, you're working.
And even when I don't feel it, you're working.
You never stop, you never stop working.
You never stop.
Because you are my way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper, light in the darkness.
My God, that is who you are.
Yes, you are my way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper, light in the darkness.
Yes, my God, that is who you are.
Yes, that is who you are.
Hello, Canvas.
My name is Andy.
I volunteer on the leadership team, along with Dave and Corey, whom you met last week.
They spoke for you.
And Amir and Andre are also on the team.
I have a wife, Emily, and we have three teenagers who live in our house and resemble us somewhat.
Emily and I have led the college Bible study at Canvas for the last few years.
By day, I am a university librarian, which is pretty much the best job ever.
We are meeting online this morning because the medical professionals in our congregation have given us that advice.
We prefer to meet in person.
We are normally at the Alamo Drafthouse in Winchester.
But the people at our church who know better than we do have suggested that this is a lot safer for now.
We are deciding this on a week by week basis for now.
Please check our website and our social media accounts and our app for updates.
We'll send out notifications each week.
If you have strong opinions about that, meeting in person versus online, I encourage you to share those with the other members of the leadership team who would be happy to talk to you about that.
And they would they would they would just love to feel those those questions.
Friends, this is a difficult Sunday for our church.
We have an important announcement following our message.
And there's a strong possibility that any anything I say this morning will be overshadowed and forgotten after that announcement.
And that's OK.
But some of us need.
Some of us need to be encouraged this week.
Some of us need to be reminded of some fundamentals.
And so we're going to do that.
We're going to do that.
Let's pray.
Heavenly Father, thank you for bringing us together today wherever we are.
Thank you for this body you have created, this little church.
Thank you for the leadership and love you've shown us.
And we pray that you would guide us moving forward.
Lord, let us hear your word this morning.
Let us hear from you and show us something new about yourself that we can take with us into next week.
Amen.
OK, so let's talk about Jesus.
In the book of John, Jesus heals a man who was born blind.
And when Jesus's enemies heard about this, they harassed this man who could now see.
And eventually they kicked him out of his synagogue.
It was a big deal because it brought disgrace on his family.
It meant he couldn't go to church anymore.
And it pretty much meant that he could never live a normal life in the community that he grew up in.
It almost made him invisible to the people that he now lived with, which is ironic because he was blind for so long.
And now they wouldn't really be seeing him the same way as they saw everyone else.
That's pretty dark.
Jesus heard about this and he searched for the man that he found him.
He went out after him and he found him.
And the man believed Jesus.
He believed the gospel just like many of us have.
A lot of us, we've learned about Jesus, how he accepted our punishment and how he died in our place.
We've learned that we are acquitted, that we're declared innocent of the fatal consequences of our sins and our failures.
And we've moved from that understanding to an acceptance that what Jesus did applies to us.
That we're the ones he came to find, that we're the ones whose sin can be taken away.
We move from that acceptance to a commitment.
To living according to Jesus' teachings.
We're loyal to Jesus now and we try to follow his pattern that he showed us and how we should treat people.
We try to serve and love the people he served and loved.
As Brandon would say, this is the poor, the powerless, and the persecuted.
And our enemies.
People who actively dislike us and do things that bother us or hurt us.
We gather together as often as possible to encourage each other.
To learn more about Jesus.
To serve each other.
And that's what the church is like.
There's more to it than that, of course.
But those are the important bits, I think.
So in John chapter 9, Jesus finds and heals a man.
In chapter 10, Jesus tells a story.
He's talking to the people who saw this miracle, who knew this man.
He's talking to his enemies, who kicked the man out of the synagogue.
And so he tells a story about sheep and shepherds and thieves or sheep nappers, I guess.
It's a sheep thief.
In the story he calls himself the good shepherd.
The good shepherd.
The good shepherd who calls his sheep by name and they recognize his voice and they follow him.
When God begins to change us, to change you and to change me, we start to recognize the good shepherd's voice.
We start to recognize the Holy Spirit moving in us, prompting us, convicting us, making us aware of the things we do that hurt each other.
We recognize the voice of the good shepherd and we start to notice what he wants from us.
We start to follow him.
St. Peter, who witnessed this whole thing, he would later tell Jesus that he's following him because Jesus has the words of life and there's no one else worth following.
And that's how many of us feel.
In John chapter 10.
Well, let's just read some.
So we're going to read John 10 verse 10.
We're going to jump around a little bit.
I don't want to read the whole chapter because you don't want to hear me talk for that long.
So I'll just read a couple verses and then skip a little bit and read a couple more verses.
John 10 verse 10.
The thief comes only to steal and kill and destroy.
This is Jesus talking.
I came that they may have life and have it abundantly.
I am the good shepherd.
The good shepherd lays down his life for the sheep.
And skipping down to verse 14.
Jesus continues and says, I'm the good shepherd.
I know my own and my own know me.
Just as my father knows me and I know the father and I lay my life down for the sheep.
There's a theme here.
Jesus is not like bad shepherds and he's not like the thieves who come to steal and kill and destroy.
He comes for the sheep.
He comes to be destroyed for the sheep.
He lays his life down for his sheep.
And he knows the sheep.
And they know his sheep.
And they know his voice.
My father would kill me if I failed to mention that this is borne out later in John.
In chapter 20, which we're not going to read, but I'll just tell you, James Montgomery Boyce points out that Mary Magdalene goes to honor Jesus's body after he was crucified.
And she finds an empty tomb and she assumes that a thief has come, a body napper and has taken away Jesus's body.
And she's weeping.
She's distraught.
She's had a pretty bad week.
Mary was rescued.
Jesus cast a lot of demons out of her.
And I just lost some of you because you're not cool with that.
But just assume demons are real for now and that Jesus freed this woman from their control, their imprisonment.
And she goes to honor his body, to prepare him ritually for a proper Jewish burial.
But she gets there.
His body's gone.
And she sees a gardener.
She looks at the gardener, doesn't know who he is.
And she asks, where have they taken my Lord?
Just tell me and I'll go get him.
And long story short, he looks at her and he says, Mary.
He just says her name.
And as soon as he says her name, she recognizes his voice.
She knows who he is.
And she rejoices because he's not as dead as she thought he was.
He's completely new and alive and different.
And it's just enacting out of Jesus's teaching.
He's a good shepherd.
He knew Mary's name.
He called her name and she recognized his voice.
When Jesus is talking about sheep and shepherds, his Jewish audience already knew all about this.
They already knew this song.
They knew the song about the good shepherd who leads a sheep to an abundant life.
They sang it all the time.
This was the song of the seasonal pilgrimage where the shepherds take their flocks from the winter shelters up through these dark canyons into the mountain pastures for them to spend the season up there all living together.
Let's read that song.
That's Psalm 23.
That'll be familiar to a lot of you.
Then we'll look at some of the details of the psalm and what it tells us about our good shepherd.
Psalm 23.
The Lord is my shepherd.
I shall not want.
He makes me lie down in green pastures.
He leads me beside still waters.
He restores my soul.
He leads me in paths of righteousness for his name's sake.
Even though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil.
For you are with me.
Your rod and your staff, they comfort me.
You prepare a table before me in the presence of my enemies.
You anoint my head with oil.
My cup overflows.
Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me all the days of my life, and I shall dwell in the house of the Lord forever.
You probably recognize that from every funeral scene in every movie you've ever seen.
Or from the Coolio song from the 90s, where Catwoman teaches a bunch of inner city youths to write poetry.
Maybe don't look that one up.
The 90s were a bit weird.
But let's go back and look through some of this.
In verse one, this is King David writing, who was an actual shepherd.
He's writing about what it's like to be a sheep.
So he is putting himself in their place, which must have been fun for him.
But he also had his share of troubles in life, and a pretty exciting story.
He writes, "The Lord is my shepherd."
Derek Kidner, who's a commentator who wrote an incredible book on Psalms,
he writes that this is the most intimate language we see so far in the Psalms for the Lord.
Up to this point, David has referred to God as his deliverer, or his king, or his shield, or his rock, or his fortress.
But shepherds are different, right?
Shepherds are everything to their flock.
The shepherd is the provider.
He feeds them directly.
He's their protector.
The shepherd's their doctor.
This is intimate language.
This is someone who is there immediately, and physically taking care of the sheep.
He makes me lie down in green pastures.
In verse two, he leads me beside still waters.
He restores my soul.
He leads me in paths of righteousness for his name's sake.
The word there in verse three, "He restores my soul."
Again, Derek Kidner points out that this is David using it in both senses.
It's a spiritual word.
So he's talking about a spiritual salvation.
But he's also referring to sheep who just wander off and need to be saved.
Sheep are kind of famous for getting themselves into trouble.
They're flock animals.
They're supposed to stick together and move around as a group.
But they get easily distracted.
Some of us know an awful lot about wandering off, about straggling behind on the path.
Jesus pursued the man that he had healed.
He went back after the fact and found him when he learned that he was in trouble.
He sensed that this man was a straggler and he went back for him.
Some of us have felt that as well.
That pursuit.
He leads me in paths of righteousness for his name's sake.
Even though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil for you are with me.
The valley of the shadow of death is highly poetic language.
And I think that's why the psalm is so popular among people who don't know anything else about the Bible.
It's just, it's a, it's beautiful, it's beautifully written.
Valley of the shadow of death.
The shadow of death is a single word in Hebrew, according to James Boyce.
And the valley of the shadow of death is a perfect, it's a fine translation.
You could also just say the darkest valley, because dark valleys can be full of death.
If you are a prey animal.
If you're a herbivore who spends life eating grass, you're well aware that there are plenty of animals that spend their lives eating sheep.
And any dark valley can be dangerous for you.
So you can call it a dark valley, you can call it a valley of shadow, you can call it the valley of the shadow of death.
Whatever name you call it, you recognize it, right?
Some of you have been there, you've, you've seen that loneliness.
You've seen that despair, or, or you've seen that grief.
And some of us are going to go into dark valleys this week, or head right back into them, and we've been in there, been there for a long time already.
Remember that that doesn't mean you're off the path.
The Good Shepherd is leading David on paths of righteousness.
And sometimes that path is beside still waters.
And sometimes that path is through the darkest valley.
But another commentator points out that it's in the valleys that we develop our character.
It's in the valleys of the shadow of death that we develop those instincts.
We, um, we start to hear and then listen to the spirit.
And we start to take good advice from more mature believers.
Um, it's in the valleys where God develops us.
So, interestingly, to me, at least, God might be the only one, but David changes his language here.
Derek Kidner points out that, um, leading up to the valley, the valley verse, before verse 4, David's saying,
"That's my shepherd up there.
That's my shepherd.
He's the one.
He leads me.
He restores me.
He does all these things."
Um, but when we get to the valley,
David's language changes.
Um,
David says, "You are with me."
You, shepherd, are close enough to talk to, not just talk about.
Now we're right here.
We can talk together.
I can talk to you.
Um,
he says, "Your rod and your staff, they comfort me."
Because now you're close enough to club the lion that's at my throat, or the wolf that's at my throat.
Um,
"You're right, you're right here with me," is the sentiment.
Verse 5.
"You prepare a table before me in the presence of my enemies.
You anoint my head with oil.
My cup overflows."
I first learned this, this psalm in the King James, so it's hard not to read, "My cup runneth over."
Um,
Whatever version you have, this is the ancient language of hospitality.
It's the ancient language of abundance, um, and of celebration.
This is food and lotion and wine.
This is rest.
Um, this is the party.
Verse 6.
"Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me all the days of my life, and I shall dwell in the house of the Lord forever."
Um,
It turns out that the word here for mercy can be translated "abundant love," and some of your Bibles have that, "abundant love."
"Your goodness and your abundant love shall follow me all the days of my life."
The word follow is not, um, just to kind of like trail behind.
Um,
This is not a comet's tail, and it's not a weird smell that follows that one kid around.
This is a pursuit.
This is a targeting.
"Surely goodness and mercy shall pursue me all the days of my life, shall come following after me."
Just like Jesus followed after people.
Um, just like the shepherd notices what sheep need to be restored.
This imagery, um, the goodness, the mercy, the table prepared, this is what Jesus meant.
Um,
Back in John 10.
Jesus says,
"I have come that they may have life and have it abundantly.
I'm the good shepherd."
This is what abundant life is like with a good shepherd.
Our daily needs are met.
We have the assurance of a heavenly home.
Um,
We have peace.
We have security.
We have contentment.
We have celebration.
We may not have all these things now.
Right now we might be in the shadow.
We might be in the dangerous valley.
But,
We have this,
We have this assurance.
That we're on the path.
That God is leading us somewhere.
And that should bring a contentment with it.
We're wrapping up.
Um,
This is a new year for our church.
We are,
We're going into it knowing that sometimes God's path for us,
Um, is shadowed and discouraging.
Sometimes that path will be beside calm restoring waters.
Um,
And in the other situation, our shepherd is beside us.
He's close enough to talk to.
Um, he's close enough to club the wolves.
We know that he won't stop leading us.
And we know where his path will take us eventually.
Um,
In the last book of the Bible.
St. John.
Who was with Jesus.
On the day he healed the man who was born blind.
Um,
He was shown a vision.
Uh,
He was shown a vision of heaven.
And,
Um,
And of a crowd of believers.
This enormous cloud of believers.
A crowd of believers.
Not a cloud.
Um,
From every nation and every race.
And,
These people had already been through the valley of the shadow of death.
And through literal death, actually.
Um,
And John asked about them.
And John was told.
Who they were.
And I'll read this.
This is Revelation 7.
Verse 16.
Um,
Pay attention to the language.
This is language we see.
Um,
From both Jesus and King David.
And,
This language should.
Should.
Okay.
This language.
Um,
It should serve.
As.
As a trigger.
That pulls us back.
To these other passages.
Um,
We should hear it.
Uh,
Tim Mackey calls these the hyperlink passages.
Where we hear these language.
These words.
And suddenly we're back in.
Psalm 23.
Or suddenly we're back.
With Jesus talking about him being a good shepherd.
Um.
So Revelation 7.
Talking about these people.
Who have been through the valley of the shadow.
They shall hunger no more.
Neither thirst anymore.
The sun shall not strike them.
Nor any scorching heat.
For the lamb in the midst of the throne.
Will be their shepherd.
He will guide them to springs of living water.
And God will wipe every tear from their eyes.
That's what we're looking forward to.
Um,
That's our certain future of an abundant life.
With the good shepherd.
We have.
A savior who was David's good shepherd.
In Psalm 23.
But willingly became a lamb.
For us.
Um.
So that through his death and resurrection.
He could lead us.
To this place that John writes about.
If you're hearing all this.
And it just all sounds crazy.
Um.
I get that.
Sometimes it sounds crazy to me too.
But if you're hearing this.
And you haven't committed yourself.
To Jesus.
You haven't accepted his offer.
Of forgiveness.
And you haven't understood.
Um.
That he wants to be your shepherd.
It's not real to you yet.
Let's talk about it.
Send.
Send us a message.
Um.
We would love to unpack that with you.
If you're already one of his sheep.
That's not real to you yet.
Let's talk about it.
Send.
Send us a message.
Um.
We would love to unpack that with you.
If you're already one of his sheep.
If you recognize that he's your shepherd.
But you're disconnected from the church.
Or if you feel yourself straggling.
Far behind the path.
Um.
Please remember that we're all prone to wander.
As the old hymn goes.
Um.
But we don't last long on our own.
Sheep belong in a flock.
And she'd need a shepherd.
Wherever your path leads you this week.
Please trust that.
There's a good shepherd who pursues you.
And who restores you.
And who knows your name.
And he'll call you.
And you'll recognize his voice.
So.
Let's pray.
Heavenly Father.
Thank you for your word.
Thank you for.
Teaching us about yourself.
Loving us enough.
To change us.
To want us to be different.
To want us to recognize you.
Um.
Thank you for loving us enough.
To know our.
Our names.
Um.
Lord.
As we go into a.
Uh.
Probably very different year for our church.
We pray that you would.
Remind us.
Of your faithfulness.
That you would.
Uh.
Reveal your will for us.
That you would.
Show us which path we're to take.
We pray these things.
In the name.
Of your son.
Our good shepherd.
And through the power of.
Your Holy Spirit.
And we trust you that.
Um.
You're going to bring.
Good out of this year.
That this will be a great year.
For our church.
That.
Um.
You're going to teach us things.
Even if it's.
Hard for us to learn them.
Amen.
Hey good morning canvas.
I uh.
Sure wish we were meeting.
In person today.
And not online.
But.
Uh.
It's just the way that.
That.
Today has played out.
With COVID.
And.
Even the possible ice storm.
That's coming.
I'm recording this.
A day in advance.
Uh.
But before we.
Get there.
I.
I wrote down.
Uh.
What I wanted to say.
To you guys today.
And.
Uh.
Are you speaking to me.
And.
In my family.
In this season.
In 2013.
Casey and I.
Launched this church.
With just 10 people.
Uh.
From a friend's basement.
Then we.
Moved.
To a small conference room.
At the Hilton.
Garden Inn.
And then.
Eventually.
Ending up.
Uh.
Going through.
And then ending up.
At the Alamo.
Where we meet today.
I have to say.
What a ride.
It's been.
In the early days.
We had no idea.
If this crazy idea.
For a church.
That we named.
Canvas.
Would or would not.
Take hold.
But boy.
Did it.
Over the last.
Eight years.
We have.
Seen God move.
In extraordinary ways.
Among other things.
We've seen many people.
Give their lives.
To Jesus.
For the first time.
And.
We've watched.
Others.
Reengage.
In their relationship.
With Jesus.
We've been.
Blown away.
To see.
How God.
Has used.
Canvas.
To impact.
Our community.
And address.
The daily.
Challenges.
Of individuals.
Experiencing.
Homelessness.
We've.
Well served.
Children.
Both.
Inside.
And outside.
Of canvas.
And even.
Received.
Sacrificially.
To families.
In need.
At Christmas.
And there's.
No telling.
How many bricks.
That we've.
Provided.
By.
Checking online.
On.
Checking in.
On Facebook.
All this.
To say.
Together.
We've.
Dreamed.
Of.
And established.
A church.
Where the broken.
And hurting.
Find.
Hope.
Healing.
Grace.
Mercy.
And love.
I'm.
So thankful.
To God.
That canvas.
Has.
Become.
Such.
A church.
Having.
First.
Planted.
And now.
Having.
Been.
The pastor.
Of canvas.
For the past.
Eight.
Years.
Has.
Been.
Truly.
A challenge.
To all.
Of us.
Individually.
And collectively.
In my.
Own.
Life.
Some.
Missteps.
On.
My.
Part.
Put.
A strain.
On.
Our.
Leadership.
Team.
Our.
Staff.
And you.
Too.
As a church.
Rather.
Than.
Trying.
To.
Navigate.
The challenges.
On.
I should.
Have.
Causing.
Such.
Strain.
And.
For.
My.
Missteps.
I really.
Am.
Truly.
Starry.
After.
Engaging.
The.
Leadership.
Team.
They.
Encouraged.
Me.
To.
Take.
Some.
Time.
And.
Where.
Next.
I intend.
To be.
As a man.
In pursuit.
Of.
God's.
Best.
Personally.
Professionally.
Spiritually.
And more.
Throughout.
That time.
The.
Expectation.
That.
I would.
Return.
To.
Normal.
At.
Canvas.
And.
Together.
We.
Had.
Hoped.
And.
Expected.
That.
Would.
Be.
To.
Do.
So.
Casey.
And.
I.
Believe.
After.
Much.
Prayer.
And.
Much.
Godly.
Counsel.
That.
God's.
Best.
For.
Us.
Our.
Family.
And.
For.
Our.
Church.
Is.
To.
Acknowledge.
That.
Our.
Time.
Here.
At.
Canvass.
Has.
Come.
To.
An.
thing to say. And it was not an easy decision for us to make. Nevertheless, we believe that it is
the right one for us to make. We are asking you to believe that with us as well. Make no mistake,
Canvas, I love you. I love this church and I'm so very proud of what God has done in and through us
over the last eight years. Please know that we will continue to wish Canvas only the best and we will
do all we can to support and assist the next lead pastor that will someday come to serve you.
In the meantime, I'll take comfort in knowing that I'm leaving Canvas in great hands. As you've seen
yourself, Ryan and Michelle have served us well over the past few months and I have no doubt that
they will continue to do the same in the future. Thanks for believing in me, loving my family, and
pursuing this incredible dream we have. Until we meet again, know that I appreciate each and every one of
you. And I am grateful for the privilege that I have had to serve you as your lead pastor. I will remember
these years well and take lessons I've learned with me into the future. And I also pray,
may God continue to uphold you in his strong and capable hands. I love you guys and I'll see you soon.
Hello, I'm back. I would like to speak on behalf of the leadership team. You should have just heard an
announcement from Pastor Brandon. The leadership team wants you to know that this is not what we
expected. It's not what we wanted for the Thomases or for the church right now. If you have questions about
about Barron's announcement, please talk to us, talk to the leadership team. We're happy to help you with
that. It's part of our job. Ryan and Michelle and Donovan and Dave and the sound crew and the other
volunteers have a lot going on. They've been carrying some extra weight the past couple months. And the
leadership team, we're happy to help clarify anything that you need to know. We'll have a lot more to say
about this in the weeks ahead as well. We'll all get together and talk through some of this. We want
you to know that we are still Canvas Church. Ryan and Michelle and the leadership team. We're not going
anywhere. We're committed to this church and we're committed to Canvas's mission to our community. That
hasn't changed. Now is an excellent time for you to get involved. We could do some help. It's very
It's a great time to volunteer, to make new friends, to start new groups, to get to know each other.
Sheep don't usually bite. We try to be friendly. We would like to thank Brandon and Casey for all their years of leading and serving and loving
this church. We believe that God is another path for them right now. Please pray for Brandon and Casey and the Thomas family.
Please pray for our church staff and our volunteers. Please pray for our church staff and our volunteers. Please pray for the people who will be discouraged by the situation.
Some of us are going to be right back in the way. We believe that God is in control and that He has a path that leads right through this into an abundant life and so we're not super discouraged.
But we know that this is a downer. Let me leave you with this benediction from the book of Hebrews.
The writer says this. Now may the God of peace, who through the blood of the eternal covenant, brought back from the dead our Lord Jesus Christ, that great shepherd of the sheep.
May that God equip you with everything good for doing His will, and may He work in us what is pleasing to Him, through Jesus Christ, to whom be glory forever and ever.
Amen. We love you. We hope to see you next week. Have a good week.
Amen.